A Guide to the Governor Robert F. McDonnell, Policy Office, Records, 1997; 2007-2014 (bulk 2010-2013)
Library of Virginia
- IV. Subject Files, 1997; 2007-2014 (bulk 2010-2013)., Extent: 18.5 cubic feet (53 boxes). (Box 57-109)
  - Subseries IV.G. Chad Cole, Scheduling Assistant, Deputy Travel Aide and Policy Assistant, 2010-2013., Extent: 0.88 cubic feet (3 boxes) (Box 102-104)
    - International Council for Local Environmental Initiatives (ICLEI), 2011. (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Pending Review, 2011. (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Local Mandates, 2012. (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Bill Signings, 2011; 2013. (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Public Safety, 2011-2012. (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - SNAP Reform, 2011. (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Regulation Documents, 2010. (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Lottery Reform, 2011. (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Veteran Affairs, 2011. (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Surplus, 2011. (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - Education Documents, 2011. (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - Bill Review, 2012. (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - SCHEV Reform, 2012. (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Commerce and Trade Work Group, 2011. (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - VRS/GACBE/Conferee, 2011. (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Bloomberg Government, 2011. (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Magazines, 2011. (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Natural Resources Work Group, 2011. (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Higher Education, 2012. (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Enrolled Bills, 2012. (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Declined Invitations, January 2013-February 2013. (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - Subseries IV.H. Policy Files, 2009-2012., Extent: 1.05 cubic feet (3 boxes) (Box 105-107)
    This subseries is housed in three (3) boxes. Arranged loosely by subject, the original has been maintained. The Policy Files appear to be from a variety of individual policy staff members. They were transferred to the Library in one record center box; many of the files were not foldered. Notable subjects include: Governor's Commission on Higher Education, Innovation and Investment, Governor's Commission on Economic Development and Job Creation, and the Governor's Commission on Government Reform and Restructuring.
    - Governor's Commission on Higher Education, Innovation and Investment, 2010-2011. (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Governor's Commission on Higher Education, Innovation and Investment, 2010-2011. (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Governor's Commission on Higher Education, Innovation and Investment, 2010-2011. (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Governor's Commission on Economic Development and Job Creation, 2010. (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Eric Finkbeiner Correspondence, 2009-2010. (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Health Care, 2009-2010. (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Energy, 2010-2011. (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Charter and Laboratory Schools, 2010. (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Israel Advisory Board, 2011. (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Governor's Commission on Government Reform and Restructuring, 2010-2011. (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Mental Health/Settlement with the U.S. Dept. of Justice, 2011. (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - K-12 Education Reform, 2011. (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Memorandum of Understanding, 2012 Governor's Holiday Hoops Classic, 2012. (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - HB 2314 (2011) Education Improvement Scholarship Act, 2011. (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Retirement System (VRS) Reform, 2011. (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - Route 460 Grundy Phase II, 2010. (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - A Report of the Secretary of Health and Human Resources to Governor Robert F. McDonnell, Recommendations Regarding the Development of a Virginia Health Benefit Exchange, 14 October 2011. (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - Technology, 2011. (Box 106, Folder 12)
    - Virginia's Budget 101, FY2011 Surplus, Highlights and Fiscal Outlook, R. Neil Miller, Deputy Secretary of Finance, 1 September 2011. (Box 106, Folder 13)
    - VDH and NRC and Dominion Power, 2011. (Box 106, Folder 14)
    - Federal Budget Trends, 2011. (Box 106, Folder 15)
    - Legislative Proposals Process for 2011 and 2012 Sessions, 2010-2011. (Box 106, Folder 16)
    - Governor McDonnell's Amendments, 2010. (Box 106, Folder 17)
    - Jobs Bills, 2010. (Box 106, Folder 18)
    - Temporary Licenses, 2010. (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Veterans Fee Waiver, SB455/HB262, 2010. (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Labor Day Talking Points from the Virginia Tourism Corporation, 2010. (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Chinese Drywall, 2010. (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Energy, 2010. (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Federal Health Care Reform, 2011. (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Social Impact Bonds, 2011. (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - K-12 Spending Data, 2011. (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Release of 2012-2014 Biennial Budget, 2011. (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - CC Letters, 2010. (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Conservation, 2010. (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - Green Energy Telebriefing, 2010. (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous Records, 2009-2010. (Box 107, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous Records, 2011. (Box 107, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous Records, 2012 and undated. (Box 107, Folder 15)
  - Subseries IV.I. Records Transferred by Northam Administration, 2011-2013 (Accession 52781)., Extent: 0.58 cubic feet (2 boxes) (Box 108-109)
    This subseries is housed in two (2) boxes. These record were found during the Northam Administration and transferred to the Library in July 2019. It is unknown why they were not transferred to the Library at the end of the McDonnell Administration in January 2014. All of the records are related to agencies and issues under the Secretary of Health and Human Resources.
    - Policy Decision Sheets, 2011-2012. (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Office of Comprehensive Services, Quarterly Report to the Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 19 September 2013. (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Homeless Outcomes Initiative, 2010-2014, Secretariats of Commerce and Trade and Health and Human Resources, October 2013. (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Department of Behavioral Health and Development Services, HHR Quarterly Meeting, 1 October 2013, presented at HHR Director's Meeting, 4 November 2013. (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Department of Social Services, Agency Work Profile, 15 October 2013. (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Department of Social Services, Agency Work Profile, 12 November 2013. (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - 2011 Legislative Proposals - Agency and Governor. (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - HB 631 and HB 825, 2012. (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Report on the Independent Reviewer on Compliance with the Settlement Agreement, United States v. Commonwealth of Virginia, 6 December 2013. (Box 109, Folder 3)